<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Del's Projects</title><link>https://www.delsprojects.co.za/</link><description>Recent content on Del's Projects</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-gb</language><copyright/><atom:link href="https://www.delsprojects.co.za/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://www.delsprojects.co.za/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.delsprojects.co.za/about/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="our-story">Our Story&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Del and his team have been serving the Rustenberg community for 5 years. What started as a one-person operation has grown into a trusted team of professionals dedicated to quality workmanship and excellent customer service.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="our-approach">Our Approach&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We believe in doing the job right the first time. Our team takes pride in providing reliable, honest service that puts your needs first. From small repairs to complex installations, we approach every job with the same level of care and attention to detail.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Services</title><link>https://www.delsprojects.co.za/services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.delsprojects.co.za/services/</guid><description>&lt;p>We proudly serve Rustenburg and surrounding communities within a 30km radius.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="plumbing-services">Plumbing Services&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Emergency Repairs&lt;/strong> - Fast response to leaks, blockages, and other plumbing emergencies&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Fixture Installation&lt;/strong> - Sinks, toilets, showers, and bathtubs&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Pipe Repairs and Replacement&lt;/strong> - Fixing leaks, frozen pipes, and damaged plumbing&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Drain Cleaning&lt;/strong> - Removing blockages and ensuring proper water flow&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Water Geyser Services&lt;/strong> - Installation, maintenance, and repair&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="handyman-services">Handyman Services&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Small Repairs&lt;/strong> - General fixes around your home or business&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Signage&lt;/strong> - We can make and install any signs to your specification&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Cupboard Installation&lt;/strong> - Installing your kitchen or bedroom storage solutions&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Faucet and Fixture Replacement&lt;/strong> - Updating or repairing bathroom and kitchen fixtures&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Light Fixture and Electrical Installation&lt;/strong> - Updating lighting and electrics throughout your property&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>General Maintenance&lt;/strong> - Keeping your property in top condition&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Gardening and Landscaping&lt;/strong> - Taking care of your natural surroundings&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="why-choose-us">Why Choose Us?&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Experienced Professionals&lt;/strong> - Over 20 years in the industry&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Licensed and Insured&lt;/strong> - Full coverage for your peace of mind&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Satisfaction Guaranteed&lt;/strong> - We don&amp;rsquo;t leave until the job is done right&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Competitive Pricing&lt;/strong> - Fair rates with no hidden fees&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>24/7 Emergency Service&lt;/strong> - Available when you need us most&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://www.delsprojects.co.za/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.delsprojects.co.za/contact/</guid><description>&lt;p>This is the contact form [WIP]&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>